

ABOUT ME

I am Francis Jules C. Espartero 21 years old. I choose the field of Computer Science because I wanted to create some software systems that may help in the future .I am curious on how the games, website , systems and application works using programming languages so I choose this degree to build my own website and system to be used by the users . I am talented student with industrious and systematic approach and eager to learn some information. Open and clear worker with disciplined execution, methodical excellent observational, organizational and communication skills. Extensive knowledge of re search and software skills.

CONTACT

PHONE: +639485058747

LINKEDIN:

linkedin.com/in/francis-jules-esparterob81687226

WEBSITE:

My Portfolio (francejules22.aithub.io)

FMAII.

francisjulescelesteespartero@gmail.com

HOBBIES

CREATE WEB DESIGNS

FRANCIS JULES C. ESPARTERO

JARO, ILOILO CITY PHILIPPINES

EDUCATION

COMPUTER SYSTEM SERVICING | BINGAWAN NATIONAL HIGH SCHOO 2017- 2019

WITH HIGH HONORS BEST IN ICT

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE | ILOILO SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY UNIVERSITY

2019 - 2020

DEAN LISTER (1ST & 2ND SEMESTER 2019-2020) DEAN LISTER (1ST & 2ND SEMESTER 2020-2021)

WORK EXPERIENCE

STUDENT ASSISTANT | MUNICIPALITY OF BINGAWAN JUN 2019- JUL 2019

I WAS ASSIGNED AT THE ICT OFFICE OF AND MY ROLE ARE TO CREATE ID OF CLIENT, EDIT PHOTOS AND VIDEOS USING ADOBE PHOTOSHOP, ENCODE AND UPDATE THE DATA. ALSO PROVIDE QUALITY SERVICE IN FELLOW STUDENTS AND COLLECT SOME DATA NEEDED FOR DOCUMENTATION FOR THE MUNICIPALITY OF BINGAWAN.

STUDENT ASSISTANT | ILOILO SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY UNIVERSITY AUGUST 2019 - AUGUST 2023

I AM A WORKING STUDENT AND I WAS ASSIGNED IN THE PROCUREMENT MANAGEMENT OFFICE OF MY UNIVERSITY. MY TASK ARE TO CHECK'S THE INCOMING AND OUTGOING PURCHASE REQUEST, PURCHASE ORDER, DISBURSEMENT VOUCHER AND OTHER DOCUMENTS. ALSO I RECEIVED CALLS FROM THE SUPPLIER TO ANSWER THE QUESTIONS AND QUERIES ABOUT THEIR PAPERS. LASTLY I AM TASK TO CREATE RECORDS AND UPDATE THE DATA OF THE DOCUMENTS.

SKILLS

- DATA ANALYTICS USING EXCELS, PYTHON & R PROGRAMMING
- HTML, CSS & JAVASCRIPT
- PHP & MYSQL
- CREATE DESIGN WITH FIGMA
- PRESENTATION SOFTWARE
- STRONG DECISION MAKER
- COMMUCATION AND INTERPERSONAL

